http://palmspringsinsurance.com/privacy.htm

......Commercial
General Liability also known as Business Liability is a must for any business.
Protect your company from unexpected accidents or claims, transfer the risk to
an insurance company. We have markets for Restaurants, Contractors, Retail and
any other hard to place risk. Cover your Property, Contents and all other day
to day operations. Don't lose your business to an unforseen incident.
Please
call us today for a free phone quote
Who we are
Our
website address is:
http://palmspringsinsurance.com.
What personal
data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When
visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the
comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent
string to help spam detection. An anonymized string created from your
email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service
to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is
available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your
comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of
your comment.
Media
If you
upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with
embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can
download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
We
don’t have on-site contact forms but you can contact us via email.
Cookies
If you
leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email
address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you
do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment.
These cookies will last for one year.
If you
have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary
cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains
no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When
you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login
information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two
days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select "Remember
Me", your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your
account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you
edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your
browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the
post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images,
articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact
same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These
websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional
third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded
content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if
you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
We use
Google Analytics and all collected data is anonymous.
Who
we share your data with
We do
not share collected data.
How
long we retain your data
If you
leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely.
This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments
automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For
users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal
information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit,
or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot
change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that
information.
What
rights you have over your data
If you
have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to
receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including
any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any
personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are
obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor
comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Your
contact information
We do
not share your contact information.
We use
numerous commercial data protection services and programs to keep both you
and out site safe.
What
data breach procedures we have in place?
We use
commercial firewall and data protection services.
What
third parties we receive data from?
None.
What
automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data?
None.
Industry regulatory disclosure requirements
©
2008-2019 PALMSPRINGSINURANCE.COM -GREATER PALM SPRINGS INSURANCE SERVICES
- P.S. INDEPENDENT INSURANCE SERVICES INC. CA LIC # 0L70135
WE
HAVE YOU COVERED!
©
2008 PALMSPRINGSINURANCE.COM -GREATER PALM SPRINGS INSURANCE SERVICES - P.S. INDEPENDENT
INSURANCE SERVICES INC. CA LIC # 0L70135
67850 Vista Chino, Cathedral City, CA 92234 760-320-6867 FAX 760-320-4027
TOLL FREE 800-327-7926
SERVING
THE COACHELLA VALLEY INSURANCE NEEDS FOR OVER 20 YEARS, AUTO INSURANCE, MOTORCYCLE
INSURANCE, CAR INSURANCE, HEALTH INSURANCE, LIFE INSURANCE, BOAT INSURANCE, RV INSURANCE, MOTORHOME INSURANCE, SENIOR SUPPLEMENTS, BLUE CROSS, BLUE SHIELD, ANTHEM BLUE CROSS, PACIFICARE, UNITED HEALTHCARE, CELTIC, SAFECO, HARTFORD AND BUSINESS GENERAL
LIABILITY INSURANCE. SERVING THE FOLLOWING COMMUNITIES - PALM SPRINGS, PALM DESERT,
INDIO, LA QUINTA, RANCHO MIRAGE, INDIAN WELLS, CATHEDRAL CITY, COACHELLA, THOUSAND
PALMS, DESERT HOT SPRINGS, MORONGO VALLEY, YUCCA VALLEY, JOSHUA TREE AND 29 PALMS.
RECENTLY WE HAVE EXPANDED OUR SERVICE AREAS TO RIVERSIDE, TEMECULA, SAN BERNARDINO,
BANNING, BEAUMONT, SAN DIEGO AND SURROUNDING AREAS. FREE PHONES QUOTES ARE AVAILABLE
ANYTIME DURING OFFICE HOURS. CALINSURED.COM
PALMSPRINGSINSURANCE.COM
